Finding Aid to the San Francisco Department of Public Health AIDS Office records SFH 4
San Francisco History Center, San Francisco Public Library
- Administrative Records, 1982-1994; Record Group 1; 22 Cubic Feet
  - Branch Files, 1985-1993; Subgroup 2
    - Prevention Branch, 1985-1993; Series 5
      - WEDGE, 1987-1990; Subseries 5.6
        - Production (Box 17, Folder 12)
        - Initial Press Release and Screening, September 1989 (Box 17, Folder 13)
        - Press Coverage (Box 17, Folder 14)
        - Discussion Guide (Box 17, Folder 15)
        - Project Updates to Advisory Group, December 1987 - May 1988 (Box 17, Folder 16)
        - Project Updates to Advisory Group, June 1988 - March 1989 (Box 17, Folder 17)
        - Letters From School Students To Kids In Video (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - Prevention Materials Review Process, Subseries 5.7
        - Letters from AIDS Office to CDC (Box 17, Folder 19)
        - San Francisco AID Foundation (SFAF): Crack and AIDS Brochure (Box 17, Folder 20)
        - SFAF: Positive News; Spanish, Chinese and Filipino Translations (Box 17, Folder 21)
        - SFAF: Poster Targeting Gay Latino Men (Box 17, Folder 22)
        - SFAF: "Sex Is Good" poster controversy (Box 17, Folder 23)
        - SFAF: Six other Proposals (Box 17, Folder 24)
        - National Task Force on AIDS Prevention (NTFAP): Six Projects (Box 17, Folder 25)
        - AIDS Health Project: Alternative Testing Services (ATS) Poster (Box 17, Folder 26)
        - 18th Street Services: 2 Projects (Box 17, Folder 27)
        - Bayview-Hunter's Point: Brochure "What Do These Brothers Have In Common?" (Box 17, Folder 28)
        - SFGH Patient Education Resource Center (PERC)'s Poster "Youth For Testing" (Box 17, Folder 29)
        - Filipino Task Force On AIDS: Brochure / Booklet (Box 17, Folder 30)
        - Hispanic Headquarters Advertising: Poster "We Thought We Were Too Young" (Box 17, Folder 31)
      - Marshia Herring Files, 1989-1992; Subseries 5.8
        Herring was the Prevention Branch Section Chief (per Nov. 6, 1990 org chart), Program Manager (per Jan. 1991 org chart), and/or Program Manager, Outreach and Education (per 1992 resource directory).
        - Program Review of AIDS Health Project, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 32)
        - Procedures for Contractor Selection, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 33)
        - Chronology of Problems with 1992 SFAF Contract (Box 17, Folder 34)
      - Alternative Testing Services (ATS), 1985-1994; Subseries 5.9
        - Initiation of HIV Testing in San Francisco, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 35)
        - ATS Policies and Recommendations (Box 17, Folder 36)
        - CBOs: On-site Testing Requests, March 1985 - June 198? (Box 17, Folder 37)
        - ATS Program, July 1985 - December 1985 (Box 17, Folder 38)
        - ATS Program, January 1986 - June 1987 (Box 18, Folder 1)
        - ATS Program, July 1986 - December 1986 (Box 18, Folder 2)
        - ATS Policy Manual, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 3-4)
        - Handouts and Other Information for People Testing Positive, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 5)
        - HIV Testing of Pregnant Women (Box 18, Folder 6)
        - ATS Program Evaluation, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 7)
        - Evaluation of ATS in San Francisco; Report to AIDS Office and CDC, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 8)
        - Overview of Selected Components, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 9)
        - ATS Work Group Meetings, August 1987 - January 1990 (Box 18, Folder 10-20)
        - Memos, 1988-1992 (Box 18, Folder 21)
        - Correspondence, January 1989 - November 1992 (Box 18, Folder 22)
        - Correspondence with State, July 1987 - January 1992 (Box 18, Folder 23)
        - Correspondence with AIDS Health Project, March 1988 - April 1992 (Box 18, Folder 24)
        - Ethnic Outreach (Box 18, Folder 25)
        - ATS at Center for Positive Care (Box 18, Frame 26)
        - Testing Reports, 1989-1992 (Box 18, Folder 27)
        - HIV Seroprevalence Report, July 1994 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Surveillance Branch, undated; Series 6
      - Reports, Surveys, Projections - B series (Box 22, Folder 8)
        No A series exists.
      - Reports, Surveys, Projections - C series (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Reports, Surveys, Projections - D series (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Reports, Surveys, Projections - E series (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Reports, Surveys, Projections - F series (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - CARE Files, 1988-1993; Subgroup 3
    Further divided into six series: Series 7: CARE Councils; Series 8: Local Policy Development & Community Input / Advisory Boards; Series 9: CARE Funding: Sandra Hernandez's Records; Series 10: Monitoring 1992 CARE Contracts; and Series 11: CARE Funds - RFP 172-92 (Funding for 1993).
    - CARE Council, 1989-1992; Series 7
      Further divided into two subseries: 7.1: Sophia Chang's Records; and 7.2: Sandra Hernandez's Records.
      - Sophia Chang's Records, 1990-1992; Subseries 7.1
        - Care Council: Definitions, Bylaws, Structure, Membership (Box 18, Folder 29)
        - CARE Council Minutes and Support Documents, November 1990 - October 1992; 6 folders (Box 18, Folder 30-35)
      - Sandra Hernandez's Records, Subseries 7.2
        - Task Force Members, Lists and CVs; from Don Francis's Black Book (Box 18, Folder 36)
        - Initial Documents from Mayor Agnos to Task Force Members; from Don Francis's Black Book (Box 18, Folder 37)
        - Organizing to pass Ryan White CARE Act, August 1989 - August 1990 (Box 18, Folder 38, Box 19, Folder 1)
        - Mayor's Call to Action On the HIV Epidemic, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 2)
          Sandra Hernandez's copy.
        - Reaction to Senate Vote Decimating CARE Funds, September 1990 - October 1990 (Box 19, Folder 3)
        - AIDS Funding Issues, Governor and Legislature (Box 19, Folder 4)
        - CARE Implementation; California Statewide Planning Meeting, October 1990 (Box 19, Folder 5)
        - CARE Council Manual (Box 19, Folder 6)
        - Potential New Task Force Members (Box 19, Folder 7)
        - Timeline, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 8)
        - Organizing Committee (Box 19, Folder 9)
        - Funding of HIV Task Force (Box 19, Folder 10)
        - Insurance Issues (Box 19, Folder 11)
        - MEDICAID and MEDI-CAL Issues (Box 19, Folder 12)
        - Correspondence, December 1989 - June 1990 (Box 19, Folder 13)
        - Endorsements of the Task Force Report (Mayor's Call to Action) (Box 19, Folder 14)
        - Responses to the Task Force Report (Box 19, Folder 15)
        - Organization Charts of CARE Funding (Box 19, Folder 16)
        - Drafts of Articles on CARE Funding (no author, no date) (Box 19, Folder 17)
        - Testimony from San Francisco at Rep. Boxer's Hearing, January 1990 (Box 19, Folder 18)
        - Emergency Relief for Major Affected Areas (Metropolitan Statistical Areas) (Box 19, Folder 19)
        - Mayor and Religious Leaders Meet to Address AIDS, June 1990 (Box 19, Folder 20)
        - CARE Implementation Working Meeting, Washington DC, October 25, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 21)
        - Comprehensive AIDS Resource Emergency (CARE) ACT, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 22)
        - Service Gaps and Priorities: Testimony to CARE Council (Box 19, Folder 23)
        - Mayor's HIV Task Force; Research Activities Status, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 24)
        - California AIDS Leadership Committee; Planning, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 25)
        - Model to Estimate Cost of Early Intervention for HIV in San Francisco, January 1990 (Box 19, Folder 26)
        - AIDS Budget Task Force (STATE) Final Report, May 1990 (Box 19, Folder 27)
        - AIDS Volunteer Recruitment (Box 19, Folder 28)
        - CARE Budget, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 29)
        - Prevention: Counseling / Testing
        - Cultural Competency Survey Field Test, August 1992 (Box 19, Folder 30)
        - Grand Rounds, 1990-1992 (Box 19, Folder 31)
        - Women's Health Survey (Lesbian / Bi), June 1992 (Box 19, Folder 32)
        - Women's HIV Research Issues, August 1992 (Box 19, Folder 33)
        - ACT UP Issues, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 34)
        - Early Intervention: CBO Proposals (Box 19, Folder 35)
        - Early Intervention: Program (Center for Positive Care) (Box 19, Folder 36)
        - Early Intervention: Primary Care - DPH Reports (Box 19, Folder 37)
        - Early Intervention: Prevention Branch (Box 19, Folder 38)
        - Guidelines for Initial Evaluation and Early Treatment HIV - Infected Individuals (Box 19, Folder 39)
        - CPC Plan to Health Commission, April 1991 (Box 19, Folder 40)
        - Building an HIV Community Care Network, March 1992 (Box 19, Folder 41)
        - HIV Seroprevalance Consensus Meeting, September 1991 (Box 19, Folder 42)
        - TITLE III Public Health Service (Box 19, Folder 43)
        - Housing for People with HIV-Related Dementia: NARS Study and Plan (Box 19, Folder 44)
        - Primary Care Service Providers Meeting (Box 19, Folder 45)
        - Budget Reduction Planning, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 46)
        - Recovery Values and Spirituality Conference, September 1992 (Box 19, Folder 47)
        - Primary Care Network; Dr. Ho, Community Public Health Services (Box 19, Folder 48)
        - Planning Documents
        - Reports, Various (Box 19, Folder 49)
        - Departmental Requests (Box 19, Folder 50)
        - Health Resources and Services Administration (HRSA) Service Demonstration Projects (Box 19, Folder 51)
        - CARE Implementation-Intergovernmental Agreements (Box 19, Folder 52)
        - Posting Agendas - Open Meetings (Brown Act) (Box 19, Folder 53)
        - Conflict of Interest (Box 19, Folder 54)
        - Public Inquiry [Requests for Funding] (Box 19, Folder 55)
        - Ryan White CARE Emergency Act of 1990 (Box 19, Folder 56)
        - Ryan White CARE Grant Application, October 1990 (Box 19, Folder 57)
        - Planning Process for Supplemental CARE Funds, December 1990 - March 1991 (Box 20, Folder 1)
        - CARE Funds: Application Guidelines from Health and Human Services (HHS), undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
        - CARE Funds: Supplemental Grant (Drafts), February 1991 (Box 20, Folder 3)
        - Budget Report, Formula Grant Fund, March 1991 (Box 20, Folder 4)
        - CARE Funds: Applications, February 1991, February 1992 (Box 20, Folder 5-6)
    - Local Policy Development and Community Input / Advisory Boards, 1989-1993; Series 8
      - Early Intervention Issues, Fall 1989 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - HIV Ambulatory Committee (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - HIV Substance Abuse Task Force Minutes, September 14, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Needle Exchange Community Task Force Documents, 1988-1990 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Preliminary Cost / Projections for HIV-Infected Individuals FY 1989-1993 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - Women and Early Intervention (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Health Resources and Services Administration (HRSA) Minority Funding Work papers, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Public Health Service (PHS) Grants for Minority Groups (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - Lesbian / Gay Health Services (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Department of Public Health (DPH) Women' s Health Committee (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - CARE Funding: Sandra Hernandez's Records, 1989-1992; Series 9; Boxes 20-21
      - CARE Legislation, 1989-1991 (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - Lobbying in D.C., Fall 1990 (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - CARE Act, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 19)
      - CARE Implementation, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 20)
      - Service Gaps Identified by Community-Based Organizations (CBOs), December 1990 (Box 20, Folder 21)
      - Intergovernmental Subcommittee, December 1990 - December 1992 (Box 20, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence with Department of Health and Human Services (DHHS), January 1991 - January 1992 (Box 20, Folder 23)
      - State Department of Human Services (DHS) Correspondence, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 24)
      - Memos and Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 20, Folder 25-27)
      - Correspondence with Mayor (Box 20, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence with Supervisors, Health Commission (Box 20, Folder 29)
      - Application Process Timeline (Box 20, Folder 30)
      - Service Areas Budget, Early 1991 (Box 20, Folder 31)
      - Lobbying in D.C., 1991 (Box 20, Folder 32)
      - Title II Working Group (Box 20, Folder 33)
      - Title I (Box 20, Folder 34)
      - Title I Supplemental (Box 20, Folder 35)
      - Title II (Box 20, Folder 36)
      - Title II Support Center (Box 20, Folder 37)
      - Title III (Box 20, Folder 38)
      - Uniform Reporting System, October 1991 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - CARE Awards, February 1991 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Title I Formula Grant Fund Budget Report, March 1991 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Funding People of Color (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - San Francisco General Hospital, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - CARE Applications, Various (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - CARE Application to CDC (Prevention), April 1991 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - CARE Application to CDC, May 1992 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - CARE Implementation, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - CARE Disqualifications, December 1992 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - CARE Evaluation of Programs (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - CARE Budget, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Monitoring 1992 CARE Contracts, Series 10
      - CARE Monitoring Reports A-C, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - CARE Monitoring Reports D-R, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - CARE Monitoring Reports S-Z, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - CARE Funds - RFP 172-92 (Funding for 1993), 1992-1993; Series 11
      - Receipts for Applications, Advertisements, and Bidders Conference (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Working Papers and Notes (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, December 1992 - January 1993 (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Proposals for Primary Care (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Psychosocial Support (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Eligibility (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Case Management (Box 21, Folder 22)
      - Other Health Care (Box 21, Folder 23)
      - Disqualification Letters
      - Confirmation Award Letters (Box 21, Folder 24)
      - Review Team Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 25)
      - Review Team Schedule and Lists (Box 21, Folder 26)
      - Lists and Analyses of Applications For Review (Box 21, Folder 27)
      - Review, Housing (Box 21, Folder 28)
      - Review, Case Management and Eligibility (Box 21, Folder 29)
      - Review, Primary Care (Box 21, Folder 30)
      - Review, Psychosocial Support (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Review, Other Health Care (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Housing Opportunities for Persons With AIDS (HOPWA) Letters of Intent (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - HOPWA Information for RFP 172-92 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - HOPWA Information and Correspondence on Rebidding and Defunding (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - HOPWA Other Information and Documents (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Planning Council and Legislative Information (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Contracts and Related Documents, 1984-1993; Record Group 2; 39 Cubic Feet
  - Requests for Proposals (RFPs), Series 12
    - San Francisco Department of Public Health (SFDPH) Grant Request to Department of Health and Human Services (DHHS) for Continuation of Surveillance & Investigation of AIDS, 1984-1985 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - San Francisco Department of Public Health (SFDPH) Grant Request to Department of Health and Human Services (DHHS) for Continuation of Surveillance & Investigation of AIDS, 1985-1986 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - AIDS Office Grant Application to California Department of Public Health (DPH) I&E for Risk Reduc & Provider Education, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Requirements and Instructions to Contractors in Preparing Proposals Instructions to AIDS Office Staff for Processing RFPs, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Instructions to AIDS Office Staff for Processing RFPs, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Planning of RFP for Education, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Planning of RFP for Home Health Care, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - RFP for Home Health Care, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Support Serices and Training, 1987-1988
      - Proposal Review and Monitoring (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Shanti Proposal (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Social Services and Emergency Housing: San Francisco AIDS Foundation Proposal, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Education Services: San Francisco AIDS Foundation Proposal, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Education of IV Drug Users: Instituto Familiar de la Raza (IF/R) Proposal and Review, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Home Health Care: Pacific Presbyterian Materials Review Process (PPMC) Proposal, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Home Care and In-Home Hospice Services, 1987-1988
      - RFP (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Review and Correspondence (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Visiting Nurses and Hospice Proposal (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - RFP 030: Latino Attitude Survey RFP and Info, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - RFP 031: Black Attitude Survey RFP and Info, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - RFP 046: AIDS/Substance Abuse Services, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - RFP 051: Antibody Testing Educational Material for POC, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - RFP 052: AIDS Testing Service, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - RFP 054: Case Management for Residential Program, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Prevention and Mental Health Services: Operation Concern Proposal, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Home Care: Home Care & Hospice Partial Proposal and Review, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Mental Health Services: AIDS Health Project Contract Review and Correspondence, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Prevention: Stop AIDS Project Contract Review and Correspondence, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Health Services and Prevention: Youth Projects Contract Review, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Educational Materials, 1988-1989
      - Friendship House Association of American Indians Proposal (Box 23, Folder 29)
      - Contract Processing Documents and Correspondence (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Support and Education Programs, 1988-1989
      - Shanti Proposal (Box 23, Folder 31)
      - Shanti Revised Proposal (Box 23, Folder 32)
      - Correspondence (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - RFP 007-89: Gay Male Survey
      - Bidders Conference and Description of Need (Box 23, Folder 34)
      - Review (Box 23, Folder 35)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation Proposal (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - RFP 008-89: Minority Gay / Bisexual Male Survey
      - Bidders Conference (Box 23, Folder 37)
      - Review (Box 23, Folder 38)
      - Edward Morales Proposal (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - RFP 010-89: Home Care and Hospice, RFP Development (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - RFP 046-89: Early Intervention for People of Color
      - RFP and Community Meeting (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Review and Selection (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - National Task Force on AIDS Prevention for Gay Men of Color (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - RFP 010-90: Home Care and Hospice, Bidders Conference and Description of Needs (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - RFP 071-90: Home Care Skills (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - RFP 074-90: Prevention Services for People of Color
      - Bidders Conference and Description of Need (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Working Papers and Notes (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Review (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - RFP 076-90: Prevention and Education for Gay / Bisexual Male Drug Users
      - 18th Street Services Proposal (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - RFP 077-90: Street Outreach and Evaluation
      - Bidders Conference and Description of Need (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Working Papers and Notes (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Selection Committee Report (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - Review (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - Bayview-Hunter's Point Foundation Proposal (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - California Prostitutes Education Project (CAL-PEP) Proposal (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - Glide Foundation Proposal (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - UCSF / Urban Health Study Proposal (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - RFP 080-90: Prevention and Education for Gay / Bisexual Men of Color
      - Bidders Conference and Description of Need (Box 24, Folder 22)
      - Working Papers and Notes (Box 24, Folder 23)
      - Selection Committee Report (Box 24, Folder 24)
      - Review (Box 24, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence (Box 24, Folder 26)
      - Asian and Pacific Islander Consortium on AIDS (APICA) Proposal (Box 24, Folder 27)
      - Bayview-Hunter's Point Foundation Proposal (Box 24, Folder 28)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation (SFAF), National Task Force on AIDS Prevention (NTFAP), and California Prostitues Education Project (CAL-PEP) Proposals (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - RFP 081-90: Education for Mental Health Professionals (Box 24, Folder 30)
      - Bidders Conference and Description of Need (Box 24, Folder 30)
      - Review (Box 24, Folder 31)
      - AIDS Health Project Proposal (Box 24, Folder 32)
      - Operation Concern Proposal (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - RFP 082-90: Emotional Support
      - Shanti and Gay Asian Pacific Alliance Community HIV Project (G-CHP) Proposals (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - RFP 091-90: Prevention for General Population
      - Bidders Conference and Description of Need (Box 24, Folder 35)
      - Working Papers and Notes (Box 24, Folder 36)
      - Correspondence (Box 24, Folder 37)
      - Review (Box 24, Folder 38)
      - Black Coalition on AIDS Proposal (Box 24, Folder 39)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation Proposal (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - RFP 105-90: Prevention for Asian Pacific Islander (API) Communities
      - Bidders Conference and Description of Need (Box 24, Folder 41)
      - Working Papers and Notes (Box 24, Folder 42)
      - Correspondence (Box 24, Folder 43)
      - Review (Box 24, Folder 44)
      - Asian American Recovery Services Proposal (Box 24, Folder 45)
      - Japanese Community Youth Council Proposal (Box 24, Folder 46)
      - Filipino Task Force on AIDS (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - RFP 110-91: Prevention Services for Youth
      - Community Meeting (Box 24, Folder 48)
      - Bidders Conference and Description (Box 24, Folder 49)
      - Correspondence (Box 24, Folder 50)
      - Review (Box 24, Folder 51)
      - Homeless Youth Services (Box 24, Folder 52)
    - RFP 111-91: Prevention for Women of Child Bearing Age
      - Bidders Conference and Description (Box 24, Folder 53)
      - Correspondence (Box 24, Folder 54)
      - Review (Box 24, Folder 55)
      - Community Meetings (Box 24, Folder 56)
      - AIDS Health Project Proposal (Box 24, Folder 57)
      - AIDS Intervention and Training Center Proposal (Box 24, Folder 58)
      - Asian American Recovery Services Proposal (Box 24, Folder 59)
      - California Prostitutes Education Project Proposal (Box 24, Folder 60)
      - Haight Ashbury Free Clinic, Women's Needs Center Proposal (Box 24, Folder 61)
      - HIV Center, Children's Hospital Proposal (Box 24, Folder 62)
      - Planned Parenthood Proposal (Box 24, Folder 63)
      - Women's Institute for Mental Health Proposal (Box 24, Folder 64)
    - RFP 112-91: CARE: First RFP
      - Development of Application Process (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Development of Application Letter (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Development of Contractor Selection Process (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Application Guidelines (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Sign-in Sheets (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Community Meetings (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - List of Applicants (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Psych Support Proposals (Box 25, Folder 8-9)
      - Housing Proposals (Box 25, Folder 10-11)
      - Primary Medical Care Proposals (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Other Primary Proposals (Box 25, Folder 13-15)
      - Food and Nutrition Proposals (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - Eligibility, Advocacy, and Case Management Proposals (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - Other Primary Proposals